#### **Eduardo Omine**

Front-end developer

Senior front-end developer with 15 years of professional experience.

Experienced in many types of projects, from small websites to large apps.

Experienced in front-end tools, libraries and frameworks such as **TypeScript**, **React**, **Redux**, **Next.js**, **Angular**, **RxJS**, among others.

Also experienced in back-end (PHP, MySQL, Codelgniter), mobile (React Native, Android Kotlin), and other technologies (Unity, Processing, OpenFrameworks).

Puts great *care* in code, striving for a *clear, readable, and maintainable codebase.* 

Strong background in design and typography.

Experience working in teams: agile practices, async communication, unit testing, pull requests, code reviews, CI/CD.

eduardo.omine@gmail.com http://work.omine.net/ 55 11 98618-9222

## **Recent projects**

#### **Meu Carro Novo**

Angular
June 2019 – February 2021

#### Currículo Digital (open-source)

React, Redux May 2018 – June 2019

#### **Systemweaver**

React, Next.js September – November 2019

### **Professional experience**

# Freelancer front-end developer September 2012 – (current)

Front-end developer @ Rumba July 2011 – August 2012

**Creative developer** @ Colmeia January 2008 – June 2011

Front-end developer / designer @ Gauge January 2006 – December 2007

#### Education

**MSc, Design and Architecture**University of São Paulo, 2012–2014

**BSc, Architecture and Urbanism** University of São Paulo, 1998–2002